我们创建了today_layout但是它为什么不显示呢？
We created the today layout so why doesn't it show
原因是我们现在使用的是一个简单的游标适配器。记住
up? The reason is because we're using a simple CursorAdapter. Remember
它为游标里的每一行创建了一个列表项，
that it creates a list item for every row in the
但是它仅仅支持一种项目的显示模式。也就是说
cursor but it only supports one item view type. That means
所有行里的项目必须用同一种布局。如果
that all list items must use the same layout. If
我们希望今天的预报看上去不一样，我们就需要
we want today's forecast to look differently we're going to need
创建一个自定义的游标适配器。这样我们能有多种
to create a custom CursorAdapter. That way we can have multiple
项目的显示类型。然后我们就可以基于我们正在看哪一行游标
item view types. Then we can have different list item layouts
来拥有不同的列表项。
based on what row of the cursor we're looking at.
注意，项目显示类型的概念
Note that the concept of item view types applies to
对适配器是普遍适用的，不仅仅是游标适配器。如果你打开
adapters in general, not just the CursorAdapter. If you open
游标适配器的说明文档，你可以知道这是一个抽象
up the documentation for CursorAdapter, you'll see that it's an abstract
类，包含两个抽象方法需要
class. It contains two abstract methods that you'll need to
重载, bindView方法和newView方法。
override. The bindView method as well as the newView method.
newView方法知道如何返回一个新的列表项布局，
The newView method knows how to return a new list
但还不包含任何数据。bindView方法知道
item layout, but doesn't contain data yet. The bindView method knows
如何接收一个已存在的布局并
how to take an existing layout and update
通过游标用指向的数据更新他。
it with the data pointed to by the cursor